queerty.com 2019-11-29

# Queerty Privacy Policy / Queerty

Our privacy policy is pretty simple. We respect yours, especially because without it, we wouldn’t be in business. Listen up.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

When visitors come to a Queerty, Inc. site (https://www.queerty.com or Queerty’s mobile app), we collect standard information such as their IP addresses and referral data. We also collect information visitors voluntarily submit to us, such as their names, email addresses, mailing addresses, phone numbers, interests and preferences about our services, and other personal data. Generally, this information is collected when visitors sign up for a user account, comment on our sites, initiate communication with Queerty, Inc, or enter a contest or promotion; none are required to visit or use a Queerty, Inc. site.   We do place cookies on your computer. Our cookies come may from our publishing system, our advertising server and our advertisers. Cookies help store your name or email address when commenting or logging in to a Queerty, Inc. site. Our advertisers and our ad serving technology may place cookies placed on your computer for tracking purposes.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. Visit the [Gravatar service privacy policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Registration & Email

To lessen spam and inappropriate commenters, we require registration to comment on the site.

We collect email addresses during contests or to subscribe to our newsletters.  We do not rent or sell your email or personal registration information.

You should understand that posting your email address in any visible area of our site, or in any comment, is strongly discouraged, as you are making it publicly available to others to send you unsolicited email.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage and we report information about aggregate usage (eg. how many visitors come to a certain section of the site) to current and potential advertisers.   We also use Google Analytics Advertising Features to enable better targeting and quality of Google served advertisement.  By using Queerty’s website or app, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google’s Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics and Advertising features if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or [use the opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

### Third Party Ads

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  Look for the AdChoices logo on certain ads and click it to opt-out of these practices.  If you would like to opt-out of third party advertising, each of the following programs provides an opt-out feature where consumers can choose not to receive targeted advertising from their affiliates: [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt out and the ](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)[Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) opt out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). If you are located in the European Union, you may prefer to use the EDAA opt out. Because these third parties opt-out is cookie-based, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. If you use multiple devices or browsers, you’ll have to opt out on each. If you delete the opt out cookie, you will need to opt-out again.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Our contact information

You can reach Queerty, Inc via email at holla AT queerty DOT com, or mail at:

Queerty, Inc.

584 Castro St. #623

San Francisco, CA 94114
